{
    "id": "bd8ba4c807a2439fb10e7c838461e4d5",
    "title": "Beat, Win And Lose",
    "exercises": [
        {
            "id": "3744adfdfd194c69aba499cfa0c83b09",
            "title": "Beat, Win And Lose",
            "questions": [
                {
                    "question": "Alexander the Great ……………………. every opponent between Greece and India.",
                    "description": "To beat is to defeat.",
                    "answers": [
                        "beat",
                        "won",
                        "lost"
                    ],
                    "correct": 0
                },
                {
                    "question": "He ………………………… all competition in the elections.",
                    "description": "You beat the person you are playing or fighting against.",
                    "answers": [
                        "beat",
                        "won",
                        "lost"
                    ],
                    "correct": 0
                },
                {
                    "question": "They ………………………. him to within an inch of his life.",
                    "description": "The past tense of beat is beat.",
                    "answers": [
                        "beat",
                        "beated",
                        "beaten"
                    ],
                    "correct": 0
                },
                {
                    "question": "The sea gull ………………………. its wings against the air.",
                    "description": "",
                    "answers": [
                        "beat",
                        "beated",
                        "won"
                    ],
                    "correct": 0
                },
                {
                    "question": "He …………………….. me at poker the other day.",
                    "description": "You beat the person you are playing or fighting against.",
                    "answers": [
                        "beat",
                        "won",
                        "lost"
                    ],
                    "correct": 0
                },
                {
                    "question": "He ………………………..whenever we play poker.",
                    "description": "",
                    "answers": [
                        "beats",
                        "wins"
                    ],
                    "correct": 1
                },
                {
                    "question": "India ……………………. the championship ………………………….. Australia in the final.",
                    "description": "You win an argument, game or battle and you beat the person you are playing or fighting against.",
                    "answers": [
                        "won, beating",
                        "beat, winning",
                        "won, winning"
                    ],
                    "correct": 0
                },
                {
                    "question": "The team must ……………………….. today.",
                    "description": "",
                    "answers": [
                        "win",
                        "beat"
                    ],
                    "correct": 0
                },
                {
                    "question": "The actor ………………………… an award for his role in the film.",
                    "description": "Win is the past tense of won. ",
                    "answers": [
                        "winned",
                        "win",
                        "won"
                    ],
                    "correct": 2
                },
                {
                    "question": "Opponents of the project must be ………………………… over.",
                    "description": "The past participle form of the verb is used after must be. ",
                    "answers": [
                        "win",
                        "won",
                        "winned"
                    ],
                    "correct": 1
                },
                {
                    "question": "Four more ……………………… and we will clinch the championship.",
                    "description": "When win is used as a noun, it has the plural form - wins. ",
                    "answers": [
                        "win",
                        "wins"
                    ],
                    "correct": 1
                },
                {
                    "question": "She was upset because she …………………………. the game.",
                    "description": "When you lose the game, you are beaten by your opponent.",
                    "answers": [
                        "won",
                        "beat",
                        "lost"
                    ],
                    "correct": 2
                }
            ]
        }
    ]
}